trucksandwagons.com 2017-05-23

# PRIVACY POLICY | World of trucks

Privacy Policy for www.trucksandwagons.com

All your personal information collected will be used to help you make your visit to our site as productive and enjoyable as possible.

The guarantee of the confidentiality of the personal data of the users of our site is important for www.trucksandwagons.com

Your use of www.trucksandwagons.com assumes your acceptance of this Privacy Agreement. The team at www.trucksandwagons.com reserves the right to change this agreement without prior notice. Therefore, we recommend that you check our privacy policy regularly so that you are always up-to-date.

The ads

Like other sites, we collect and use the information contained in the ads. The information contained in the advertisements includes your Internet Protocol (IP) address, ISP (Internet Service Provider such as Sapo, Clix or other), the browser you used when visiting our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox) , The time of your visit and what pages you visited on our site.

Cookie DoubleClick Dart

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to display ads on our website;

With the DART cookie, Google can display ads based on visits the reader made to other sites on the Internet;

Users can disable the DART cookie by visiting the Content Network and Google Ads Privacy Policy.

Cookies and Web Beacons

We use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when visiting our site. This can include a simple pop-up or a link to the various services we provide, such as forums.

In addition, we also use third-party ads on our site to support maintenance costs. Some of these advertisers may use technologies such as cookies and / or web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will allow these advertisers (such as Google through AdSense) to also receive their personal information such as their IP address, ISP, Browser, etc. This function is generally used for geotargeting (display advertising in Lisbon only for readers of Lisbon, for example) or display targeted advertising for a user type (such as showing restaurant advertising to a user visiting regular cooking venues) .

You have the power to disable cookies, browser options, or make changes to anti-virus software tools, such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can change the way you interact with our site or other sites. This may or may not affect your ability to sign in to programs, websites, or forums from our and other networks.

Links to Third Party Sites

Www.trucksandwagons.com has links to other sites that we believe may contain helpful information / tools for our visitors. Our privacy policy is not applied to third party sites, so if you visit another site of our site, you should read the privacy policy of the site.

We are not responsible for the privacy policy or content present on those same sites.
